{
  "data": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which of the following css property is used to make an element move from a particular direction to another...",
      "answer": "flex-direction",
      "a": "justify-content",
      "b": "align-items",
      "c": "flex-direction",
      "d": "display: flex"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which of the following css property is used to make an element move horizontally from a particular direction to another...",
      "answer": "justify-content",
      "a": "justify-content",
      "b": "align-items",
      "c": "flex-end",
      "d": "flex-start"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which of the following css property is used to make an element move vertically from a particular direction to another...",
      "answer": "align-items",
      "a": "flex-start",
      "b": "space-around",
      "c": "justify-content",
      "d": "align-items"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What is the full meaning of HTML...",
      "answer": "Hyper-Text Markup Language",
      "a": "Hype-Transfer Marking Language",
      "b": "Hyper-Text Model Language",
      "c": "Hyper-Text Markup Language",
      "d": "Hyper-Text Morkup Language"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What is the full meaning of CSS...",
      "answer": "Cascading Style Sheet",
      "a": "Cascader Styler Sheets",
      "b": "Cascading Style Sheet",
      "c": "Card Styles Sheets",
      "d": "Computing Styled Sheet"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The following are examples of Text Editors used for coding...",
      "answer": "Notepad, Visual Studio Code",
      "a": "Ms-Server, Notes",
      "b": "Ms-word, Ms-excel",
      "c": "Notebox++, Vs-Version",
      "d": "Notepad, Visual Studio Code"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which of the following tags are used for creating links",
      "answer": "<a>Tag",
      "a": "<h1>Tag",
      "b": "<head>Tag",
      "c": "<title>Tag",
      "d": "<a>Tag"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "The extension that is used when creating an HTML File is called...",
      "answer": ".html extention",
      "a": ".css extension",
      "b": "cmd extension",
      "c": ".ts extention",
      "d": ".html extention"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which of the following term is used when refering to defining the skeleton of a webpage...",
      "answer": "HTML",
      "a": "HTML",
      "b": "CSS",
      "c": "Boxification",
      "d": "Website"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Identify a self-closing tag",
      "answer": "<br/>",
      "a": "</br>",
      "b": "<br></br>",
      "c": "<br/>",
      "d": "<br>"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "What is the current version of HTML",
      "answer": "HTML5",
      "a": "HXML5",
      "b": "HTML5",
      "c": "XML5",
      "d": "HTML25"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Browser used in viewing your result when done coding are all except one ",
      "answer": "Google Earth",
      "a": "Google chrome",
      "b": "Firefox",
      "c": "Google Earth",
      "d": "Opera mini"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "What property is used to change the default color of a text to another color",
      "answer": "color",
      "a": "background-color",
      "b": "border-color",
      "c": "text-color",
      "d": "color"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "What html tag is used to make a text bold",
      "answer": "<b></b>",
      "a": "<b></b>",
      "b": "<bold></bold>",
      "c": "<large></large>",
      "d": "<big></big>"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "What css property is used to make your text bold",
      "answer": "font-weight",
      "a": "text-size",
      "b": "font-family",
      "c": "font-width",
      "d": "font-weight"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "These are html tags except one",
      "answer": "<bi></bi>",
      "a": "<i></i>",
      "b": "<h2></h2>",
      "c": "<bi></bi",
      "d": "<h1></h1>"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Which of the following symbols signifies that a particular tag has a 'Class' ",
      "answer": ".",
      "a": "*",
      "b": "-",
      "c": "!",
      "d": "."
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Which of the following symbols signifies that a particular tag has an 'ID' ",
      "answer": "#",
      "a": "*",
      "b": "-",
      "c": "$",
      "d": "#"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "What is the unit of measurement for font size in CSS?",
      "answer": "px",
      "a": "%",
      "b": "vm",
      "c": "px",
      "d": "pz"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "What is the purpose of the `<img>` tag?",
      "answer": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an image into a web page.",
      "a": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an icon into a web page.",
      "b": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an image into a web page.",
      "c": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an imagination into a web page.",
      "d": "The `<img>` tag is used to insert an complier into a web page."
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "What is the purpose of the `DOCTYPE` declaration?",
      "answer": "It is used to declare the type of document that is being created.",
      "a": "It is used to declare the type of document that is being created.",
      "b": "It is used to deleted the type of document that is being created.",
      "c": "It is used to format the type of document that is being created.",
      "d": "It is used to modify the type of document that is being created."
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "With what exact Tags can a list be created in HTML?",
      "answer": "<ul>&<ol>",
      "a": "<list>&<ol>",
      "b": "<il>&<ul>",
      "c": "<ul>&<ol>",
      "d": "<il>&<list>"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "What is the closing tag for a paragraph element?",
      "answer": "</p>",
      "a": "<p/>",
      "b": "</pg>",
      "c": "</p>",
      "d": "<pg/>"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Which CSS property enables the manipulation of spaces around a container?",
      "answer": "margin",
      "a": "margin",
      "b": "padding",
      "c": "flex",
      "d": "position"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Which CSS property enables the manipulation of spaces inside of a container?",
      "answer": "padding",
      "a": "margin",
      "b": "padding",
      "c": "flex",
      "d": "position"
    }
  ]
}